Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Degrees voted, 1968 -- 2001; UA002.007; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Degrees voted, Spring vote, 1970; UA002.007.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Fall vote, 1970; UA002.007.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklet, 1971; UA002.007.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Spring vote, 1971; UA002.007.041.00006 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.007.041.00007 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, October vote, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.007.041.00008 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, March vote, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.007.041.00009 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, June vote, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.007.041.00010 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.007.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, October 28, 1972 vote, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.007.041.00012 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, March 27, 1973 vote, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.007.041.00013 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, June 2, 1973 vote, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.007.041.00014 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.007.041.00015 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 3, 1973 vote, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.007.041.00016 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, March 26, 1974 vote, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.007.041.00017 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, June 14, 1974 vote, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.007.041.00018 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.007.041.00019 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 2, 1974 vote, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.007.041.00020 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 25, 1975 vote, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.007.041.00021 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 24, 1975 vote, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.007.041.00022 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1975 -- 1976; UA002.007.041.00023 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 1, 1975 vote, 1975 -- 1976; UA002.007.041.00024 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, March 26, 1976 vote, 1975 -- 1976; UA002.007.041.00025 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 22, 1976 vote, 1975 -- 1976; UA002.007.041.00026 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.007.041.00027 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, October 30, 1976 vote, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.007.041.00028 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, March 26, 1977 vote, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.007.041.00029 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 21, 1977 vote, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.007.041.00030 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklet, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.007.041.00031 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 5, 1977 vote, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.007.041.00032 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 25, 1978 vote, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.007.041.00033 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 20, 1978 vote, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.007.041.00034 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.007.041.00035 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, October 28, 1978 vote, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.007.041.00036 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 24, 1979 vote, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.007.041.00037 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 19, 1979 vote, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.007.041.00038 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.007.041.00039 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 3, 1979 vote, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.007.041.00040 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 23, 1980 vote, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.007.041.00041 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 24, 1980 vote, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.007.041.00042 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.007.041.00043 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 1, 1980 vote, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.007.041.00044 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 28, 1981 vote, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.007.041.00045 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 30, 1981 vote, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.007.041.00046 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1981 -- 1982; UA002.007.041.00047 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, October 24, 1981 vote, 1981 -- 1982; UA002.007.041.00048 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 27, 1982 vote, 1981 -- 1982; UA002.007.041.00049 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 29, 1982 vote, 1981 -- 1982; UA002.007.041.00050 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.007.041.00051 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, November 6, 1982 vote, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.007.041.00052 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, February 26, 1983 vote, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.007.041.00053 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, May 28, 1983 vote, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.007.041.00054 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklet, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.007.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 5, 1983 vote, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.007.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 25, 1984 vote, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.007.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 19, 1984 vote, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.007.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.007.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 3, 1984 vote, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.007.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 23, 1985 vote, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.007.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 18, 1985 vote, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.007.042.00008 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.007.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 9, 1985 vote, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.007.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 22, 1986 vote, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.007.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 17, 1986 vote, 1985 -- 1986; UA002.007.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.007.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 15, 1986 vote, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.007.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 28, 1987 vote, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.007.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 16, 1987 vote, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.007.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.007.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 14, 1987 vote, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.007.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 27, 1988 vote, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.007.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 21, 1988 vote, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.007.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.007.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 5, 1988 vote, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.007.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 25, 1989 vote, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.007.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 20, 1989 vote, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.007.042.00024 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1989 -- 1990; UA002.007.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 4, 1989 vote, 1989 -- 1990; UA002.007.042.00026 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 24, 1990 vote, 1989 -- 1990; UA002.007.042.00027 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 19, 1990 vote, 1989 -- 1990; UA002.007.042.00028 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.007.042.00029 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 3, 1990 vote, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.007.042.00030 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 23, 1991 vote, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.007.042.00031 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 11, 1991 vote, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.007.042.00032 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1991 -- 1992; UA002.007.042.00033 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 2, 1991 vote, 1991 -- 1992; UA002.007.042.00034 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 29, 1992 vote, 1991 -- 1992; UA002.007.042.00035 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 16, 1992 vote, 1991 -- 1992; UA002.007.042.00036 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.007.042.00037 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, November 7, 1992 vote, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.007.042.00038 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, February 27, 1993 vote, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.007.042.00039 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, May 22, 1993 vote, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.007.042.00040 (Box 42)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1993 -- 1994; UA002.007.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 6, 1993 vote, 1993 -- 1994; UA002.007.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 26, 1994 vote, 1993 -- 1994; UA002.007.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 21, 1994 vote, 1993 -- 1994; UA002.007.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1994 -- 1995; UA002.007.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 14, 1994 vote, 1994 -- 1995; UA002.007.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 11, 1995 vote, 1994 -- 1995; UA002.007.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 20, 1995 vote, 1994 -- 1995; UA002.007.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.007.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 4, 1995 vote, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.007.043.00010 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 10, 1996 vote, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.007.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 18, 1996 vote, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.007.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.007.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 2, 1996 voted, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.007.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 8, 1997 vote, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.007.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 17, 1997 vote, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.007.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.007.043.00017 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, September 9, 1997 vote, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.007.043.00018 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 8, 1997 vote, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.007.043.00019 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 9, 1998 vote, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.007.043.00020 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 16, 1998 vote, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.007.043.00021 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.007.043.00022 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, September 3, 1998 vote, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.007.043.00023 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 7, 1998 vote, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.007.043.00024 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 6, 1999 vote, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.007.043.00025 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 22, 1999 vote, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.007.043.00026 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklet, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.007.043.00027 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, September 7, 1999 vote, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.007.043.00028 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 6, 1999 vote, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.007.043.00029 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 12, 2000 vote, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.007.043.00030 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 20, 2000 vote, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.007.043.00031 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklet, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.007.043.00032 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, September 5, 2000 vote, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.007.043.00033 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, November 4, 2000 vote, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.007.043.00034 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, February 10, 2001 vote, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.007.043.00035 (Box 43)
  - Degrees voted, May 19, 2001 vote, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.007.043.00036 (Box 43)
- Faculty records, 1924 -- 2012; UA002.008; 19.7 Linear Feet
  This series contains personnel related information regarding Tufts faculty. The series contains primarily Appointment Record Cards used to track faculties' personal information and appointment records. Also included are correspondence, tenure information, and curriculum vitae.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by faculty member's last name
  - A-B, 1 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - A-B, 2 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - A-B, 3 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - C-D, 1 of 5, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00004 (Box 44)
  - C-D, 2 of 5, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - C-D, 3 of 5, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - C-D, 4 of 5, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00007 (Box 44)
  - C-D, 5 of 5, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00008 (Box 44)
  - E-F, 1 of 2, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00009 (Box 44)
  - E-F, 2 of 2, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00010 (Box 44)
  - G-H, 1 of 4, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00011 (Box 44)
  - G-H, 2 of 4, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00012 (Box 44)
  - G-H, 3 of 4, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00013 (Box 44)
  - G-H, 4 of 4, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.044.00014 (Box 44)
  - I-J-K, 1 of 6, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00001 (Box 45)
  - I-J-K, 2 of 6, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00002 (Box 45)
  - I-J-K, 3 of 6, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00003 (Box 45)
  - I-J-K, 4 of 6, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00004 (Box 45)
  - I-J-K, 5 of 6, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00005 (Box 45)
  - I-J-K, 6 of 6, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 1 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00007 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 2 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00008 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 3 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00009 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 4 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00010 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 5 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00011 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 6 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00012 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 7 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00013 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 8 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00014 (Box 45)
  - L-N, 9 of 9, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.045.00015 (Box 45)
  - O-Q, 1 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - O-Q, 2 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - O-Q, 3 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - R-S, 1 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - R-S, 2 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - R-S, 3 of 3, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - T-U, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00007 (Box 46)
  - V-Z, 1943 -- 1985; UA002.008.046.00008 (Box 46)
  - A, 1 of 4, 1932 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00001 (Box 49)
  - A, 2 of 4, 1932 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - A, 3 of 4, 1932 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00003 (Box 49)
  - A, 4 of 4, 1932 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00004 (Box 49)
  - B, 1 of 6, 1934 -- 2004; UA002.008.049.00005 (Box 49)
  - B, 2 of 6, 1934 -- 2004; UA002.008.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - B, 3 of 6, 1934 -- 2004; UA002.008.049.00007 (Box 49)
  - B, 4 of 6, 1934 -- 2004; UA002.008.049.00008 (Box 49)
  - B, 5 of 6, 1934 -- 2004; UA002.008.049.00009 (Box 49)
  - B, 6 of 6, 1934 -- 2004; UA002.008.049.00010 (Box 49)
  - C, 1 of 6, 1949 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00011 (Box 49)
  - C, 2 of 6, 1949 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00012 (Box 49)
  - C, 3 of 6, 1949 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00013 (Box 49)
  - C, 4 of 6, 1949 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00014 (Box 49)
  - C, 5 of 6, 1949 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00015 (Box 49)
  - C, 6 of 6, 1949 -- 2005; UA002.008.049.00016 (Box 49)
  - D, 1 of 4, 1954 -- 2000; UA002.008.049.00017 (Box 49)
  - D, 2 of 4, 1954 -- 2000; UA002.008.049.00018 (Box 49)
  - D, 3 of 4, 1954 -- 2000; UA002.008.049.00019 (Box 49)
  - D, 4 of 4, 1954 -- 2000; UA002.008.049.00020 (Box 49)
  - E, 1 of 2, 1970 -- 2005; UA002.008.050.00001 (Box 50)
  - E, 2 of 2, 1978 -- 1995; UA002.008.050.00002 (Box 50)
  - F, 1 of 4, 1955 -- 2007; UA002.008.050.00003 (Box 50)
  - F, 2 of 4, 1953 -- 2003; UA002.008.050.00004 (Box 50)
  - F, 3 of 4, 1953 -- 2001; UA002.008.050.00005 (Box 50)
  - F, 4 of 4, 1957 -- 2006; UA002.008.050.00006 (Box 50)
  - G, 1 of 3, 1957 -- 2007; UA002.008.050.00007 (Box 50)
  - G, 2 of 3, 1954 -- 2000; UA002.008.050.00008 (Box 50)
  - G, 3 of 3, 1971 -- 2004; UA002.008.050.00009 (Box 50)
  - H, 1 of 5, 1964 -- 2005; UA002.008.050.00010 (Box 50)
  - H, 2 of 5, 1971 -- 2003; UA002.008.050.00011 (Box 50)
  - H, 3 of 5, 1961 -- 1998; UA002.008.050.00012 (Box 50)
  - H, 4 of 5, 1954 -- 2002; UA002.008.050.00013 (Box 50)
  - H, 5 of 5, 1956 -- 2004; UA002.008.050.00014 (Box 50)
  - I, 1 of 1, 1974 -- 1989; UA002.008.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - J, 1 of 2, 1961 -- 2000; UA002.008.051.00002 (Box 51)
  - J, 2 of 2, 1961 -- 2000; UA002.008.051.00003 (Box 51)
  - K, 1 of 2, 1967 -- 2001; UA002.008.051.00004 (Box 51)
  - K, 2 of 2, 1965 -- 2001; UA002.008.051.00005 (Box 51)
  - L, 1 of 3, 1951 -- 2003; UA002.008.051.00006 (Box 51)
  - L, 2 of 3, 1972 -- 2000; UA002.008.051.00007 (Box 51)
  - L, 3 of 3, 1970 -- 2003; UA002.008.051.00008 (Box 51)
  - M, 1 of 8, 1971 -- 2004; UA002.008.051.00009 (Box 51)
  - M, 2 of 8, 1970 -- 1996; UA002.008.051.00010 (Box 51)
  - M, 3 of 8, 1958 -- 2008; UA002.008.051.00011 (Box 51)
  - M, 4 of 8, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.008.051.00012 (Box 51)
    Jean Mayer
  - M, 5 of 8, 1950 -- 2002; UA002.008.051.00013 (Box 51)
  - M, 6 of 8, 1953 -- 2000; UA002.008.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - M, 7 of 8, 1965 -- 2000; UA002.008.052.00002 (Box 52)
  - M, 8 of 8, 1954 -- 2002; UA002.008.052.00003 (Box 52)
  - N, 1 of 2, 1959 -- 2004; UA002.008.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - N, 2 of 2, 1953 -- 1999; UA002.008.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - O, 1 of 1, 1965 -- 1997; UA002.008.052.00006 (Box 52)
  - P, 1 of 5, 1971 -- 1992; UA002.008.052.00007 (Box 52)
  - P, 2 of 5, 1955 -- 2002; UA002.008.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - P, 3 of 4, 1953 -- 2004; UA002.008.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - P, 4 of 4, 1955 -- 2004; UA002.008.052.00010 (Box 52)
  - Q, 1 of 1, 1965 -- 1980; UA002.008.052.00011 (Box 52)
  - R, 1 of 7, 1952 -- 1998; UA002.008.052.00012 (Box 52)
  - R, 2 of 7, 1952 -- 1998; UA002.008.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - R, 3 of 7, 1955 -- 1995; UA002.008.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - R, 4 of 7, 1994; UA002.008.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - R, 5 of 7, 1953 -- 1995; UA002.008.053.00002 (Box 53)
  - R, 6 of 7, 1953 -- 1996; UA002.008.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - R, 7 of 7, 1952 -- 2002; UA002.008.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - S, 1 of 9, 1952 -- 2003; UA002.008.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - S, 2 of 9, 1952 -- 2003; UA002.008.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - S, 3 of 9, 1952 -- 2002; UA002.008.053.00007 (Box 53)
  - S, 4 of 9, 1955 -- 2002; UA002.008.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - S, 5 of 9, 1952 -- 2001; UA002.008.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - S, 6 of 9, 1956 -- 1998; UA002.008.053.00010 (Box 53)
  - S, 7 of 9, 1953 -- 1998; UA002.008.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - S, 8 of 9, 1953 -- 1998; UA002.008.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - S, 9 of 9, 1960 -- 1983; UA002.008.054.00002 (Box 54)
  - T, 1 of 3, 1967 -- 1997; UA002.008.054.00003 (Box 54)
  - T, 2 of 3, 1958 -- 1998; UA002.008.054.00004 (Box 54)
  - T, 3 of 3, 1953 -- 2003; UA002.008.054.00005 (Box 54)
  - U, 1 of 1, 1952 -- 2006; UA002.008.054.00006 (Box 54)
  - V, 1 of 2, 1963 -- 1997; UA002.008.054.00007 (Box 54)
  - V, 2 of 2, 1958 -- 1998; UA002.008.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - W, 1 of 5, 1956 -- 2002; UA002.008.054.00009 (Box 54)
  - W, 2 of 5, 1953 -- 2000; UA002.008.054.00010 (Box 54)
  - W, 3 of 5, 1954 -- 1996; UA002.008.054.00011 (Box 54)
  - W, 4 of 5, 1957 -- 2001; UA002.008.054.00012 (Box 54)
  - W, 5 of 5, 1954 -- 1997; UA002.008.054.00013 (Box 54)
  - X-Y, 1 of 1, 1954 -- 2006; UA002.008.054.00014 (Box 54)
  - Z, 1 of 2, 1962 -- 1996; UA002.008.054.00015 (Box 54)
  - Z, 2 of 2, 1963 -- 1996; UA002.008.054.00016 (Box 54)
  - Faculty Census, 1959 -- 1979; UA002.008.058.00001 (Box 58)
  - Salary and other information, 1953 -- 1969; UA002.008.058.00002 (Box 58)
  - Salary and other information, 1958 -- 1960; UA002.008.058.00003 (Box 58)
  - Salary and other information, 1959 -- 1960; UA002.008.058.00004 (Box 58)
  - Salary and other information, 1960 -- 1972; UA002.008.058.00005 (Box 58)
  - AAUP Salary Surveys and Information [1 of 2], 1961 -- 1962; UA002.008.058.00006 (Box 58)
  - AAUP Salary Surveys and Information [2 of 2], 1961 -- 1962; UA002.008.058.00007 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information [1 of 2], 1962 -- 1964; UA002.008.058.00008 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information [2 of 2], 1962 -- 1964; UA002.008.058.00009 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information, 1963 -- 1964; UA002.008.058.00010 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information and Surveys, 1954 -- 1965; UA002.008.058.00011 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information, 1965 -- 1966; UA002.008.058.00012 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information, 1966 -- 1967; UA002.008.058.00013 (Box 58)
  - Salary Information, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.008.058.00014 (Box 58)
  - Teaching loads, 1969 -- 1970; UA002.008.058.00015 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1969 -- 1970; UA002.008.058.00016 (Box 58)
  - Salary files, 1969 -- 1970; UA002.008.058.00017 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1970 -- 1971; UA002.008.058.00018 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.008.058.00019 (Box 58)
  - Teaching loads, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.008.058.00020 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1972 -- 1973; UA002.008.058.00021 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1973 -- 1974; UA002.008.058.00022 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1974 -- 1975; UA002.008.058.00023 (Box 58)
  - Salary study, 1975; UA002.008.058.00024 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1975 -- 1976; UA002.008.058.00025 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1976 -- 1977; UA002.008.058.00026 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1977 -- 1978; UA002.008.058.00027 (Box 58)
  - Salary and Other Information, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.008.058.00028 (Box 58)
  - HEGIS, 1979 -- 1980; UA002.008.058.00029 (Box 58)
  - Faculty Footprints, 1985 -- 1987; UA002.008.058.00030 (Box 58)
  - Faculty Teaching Loads and Class Schedules, 1982 -- 1987; UA002.008.058.00031 (Box 58)
  - Faculty Annual, 1983; UA002.008.058.00032 (Box 58)
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine Cirriculum Procedures Manual, 2002 -- 2003; UA002.008.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine Bylaws of the Faculty, 1994; UA002.008.066.00002 (Box 66)
  - Health Sciences Deans Council (One Medicine), 1986 -- 1988; UA002.008.066.00003 (Box 66)
  - Tufts University Faculty and Staff Affirmative Action Plan, 2004; UA002.008.066.00004 (Box 66)
  - TUSDM Student Handbook, 2002; UA002.008.066.00005 (Box 66)
  - University-Wide Review of Graduate Programs, 2001; UA002.008.066.00006 (Box 66)
  - Graduate Programs of Tufts University in Arts & Sciences and Engineering: A Self-Assessment and Strategic Plan for the Future, Spring 2001, UA002.008.066.00007 (Box 66)
  - Faculty Data, Academic Affairs Committee, 2007; UA002.008.066.00008 (Box 66)
  - A Blueprint for Tufts Tomorrow, 1996; UA002.008.066.00009 (Box 66)
  - Aldema-Ramos, Mila, 2006; UA002.008.066.00010 (Box 66)
  - Banks, Peter, 1992; UA002.008.066.00011 (Box 66)
  - Bartlett, John, 1980; UA002.008.066.00012 (Box 66)
  - Benotti, Peter, 1999; UA002.008.066.00013 (Box 66)
  - Berkowitz, David, 1999; UA002.008.066.00014 (Box 66)
  - Cullen, David, 2005; UA002.008.066.00015 (Box 66)
  - Curry, Steven, 1989; UA002.008.066.00016 (Box 66)
  - Donowitz, Mark, 1988; UA002.008.066.00017 (Box 66)
  - Folstein, Susan, 2004; UA002.008.066.00018 (Box 66)
  - Fulton, David, 1998; UA002.008.066.00019 (Box 66)
  - Hutchinson, Martha, 1998; UA002.008.066.00020 (Box 66)
  - Kelleher, John, 2000; UA002.008.066.00021 (Box 66)
  - Krontiris, Theodore, 1996; UA002.008.066.00022 (Box 66)
  - Losordo, Douglas, 2006; UA002.008.066.00023 (Box 66)
  - Markey, Caroline, 2003; UA002.008.066.00024 (Box 66)
  - Mermin, Naomi, 2006; UA002.008.066.00025 (Box 66)
  - Rufo, Myra, 2004; UA002.008.066.00026 (Box 66)
  - Shapiro, Jay, 1986; UA002.008.066.00027 (Box 66)
  - Shapiro, Morrill, UA002.008.066.00028 (Box 66)
  - Simmons, Christine, 1993; UA002.008.066.00029 (Box 66)
  - Shapiro, Morris, UA002.008.066.00030 (Box 66)
  - Sloan, Nancy, 2006; UA002.008.066.00031 (Box 66)
  - Turner, Roderick, UA002.008.066.00032 (Box 66)
  - Exec. Asst. to Pres. (Search), 1992; UA002.008.066.00033 (Box 66)
  - Vet Dean Seach, 1995 -- 1997; UA002.008.066.00034 (Box 66)
  - Veterinary School Dean Search, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.008.066.00035 (Box 66)
  - Presidential Search, 2000 -- 2001; UA002.008.066.00036 (Box 66)
  - Fletcher Dean Search, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.008.066.00037 (Box 66)
  - Sackler School Dean Search, 2001 -- 2002; UA002.008.066.00038 (Box 66)
  - Medical Dean Search, 1996 -- 2003; UA002.008.066.00039 (Box 66)